Every ten seconds, she gets all giggly.
Probably doesn't realize she's doing it.
Leave her be.
Oh no.
I'm not concentrating at all!
I keep spacing out.
We got back from camping yesterday,
and it's finally sinking in...
That Akira-san and I...
kissed.
That was my... first kiss, right?
Hey, she's giggling again.
I mean, I've never had
any romantic experiences!
Has she been like this all day?
Yeah. Broken record since this morning.
Shizuka-san. I'm sorry for the wait.
No problem!
Shall we head home now?
Y-Yes...
Oh, right.
What would you think of
stopping by a bar after dinner?
What's the matter?
I... I was just thinking... it's nice
that you're so unaffected by it all...
I mean, the fact you're
so calm and collected!
I almost feel like
I should take offense at that.
I-I'm sorry!
Shizuka-san. Your hand, please.
Remember what I told you at the start?
I don't want you thinking you're
the only one who's nervous.
W-Well...
I was completely beside myself
on the bench that day.
I'm sure you realized that.
He's pressed against
my back... He's so warm!
Or do you dislike men
who aren't always the picture of dignity?
Actually, I lo—
I prefer them.
Did you just change your wording?
One Scarlett O'Hara.
Here you are.
Thank you.
The glass seems very small.
It's a cocktail glass.
Do you go to bars?
I'm afraid not.
It's pretty rare for me
to drink outside my home.
Do most people come to bars to drink?
Yes, they're a place you go to enjoy
the pure pleasure of drinking.
Or when you want to spend
more time with someone.
Everything he says makes
my heart skip a beat!
I need to toughen up!
I recommend the fruity cocktails here.
Is it okay for you to drink so fast?
Shizuka-san?
You're over here, right, Akira-san?
Yes...
I'm gonna sit by your side.
R-Right.
What is it?
I need to tell you...
I have no romantic experience!
I'm sure you're disgusted
by my unrelenting childishness!
I'm really not.
I'm older, anyway, so don't—
Do not interrupt!
Right.
That kiss, too...
I-It was my first.
Forgive me, okay?
Did I sound like a child there too?!
No, not at all!
I'm not trying to make you uncomfortable!
You're really not.
Why does she always want
forgiveness for things?
Though, I've seen hints
of that since our first date...
Let's just have some water for now.
Excuse me. Water, please.
Coming up.
Akira-san's so quiet.
Why did I say all that nonsense?!
Shizuka-san. We're here.
R-Right!
Driver, could you wait here for a minute?
Um... Would you like to come in for tea?
Not today, please.
He's disgusted with me!
Well... Thank you
for getting me home safe.
Shizuka-san.
Yes?
I can tell you have complicated feelings
about what we talked about today.
But please...
give me permission to treasure you.
Akira-san...
I-I feel more than
adequately treasured by you!
You even gave me that raise earlier!
Well, thank you for that.
I can go home with a light heart, then.
What do you mean by that?!
Akira-san! Akira-san!
It's raining so hard!
Sh-Shizuka-san!
A-Akira-san.
It's raining so hard out there.
I'm just miserable!
Even my handkerchief is soaked!
Th-That sounds awful.
I put a heater on the table by the sofa,
so make yourself at home.
Here's a towel for you, too.
Oh, thank you!
You seem very well prepared...
Did you get rained on, too?
No, I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
I see.
Even my undershirt is soaked!
I-I'll find you a blanket!
I really appreciate that!
I'm sorry. It took some time to find one.
Here.
Thank yo—
Your hands are wet. And they're cold.
Your clothing's soaked, too!
You're not fine at all!
You took advantage
of my blindness, darn you!
I-I'm sorry.
It's still raining, huh?
Yes.
The heater's nice and warm, huh?
Um...
We're pressed together!
And he's calm and I'm a mess!
I'm so embarrassed!
That's Akira-san's hand!
I should return the gesture somehow!
Excuse me...
Getting to do this with you...
It makes me... very happy.
Shizuka-san.
Is he going to... kiss me?
It's pouring buckets out there!
Did you guys get rained on as well?
Y-Yes, we did!
Let me adjust the temperature here...
It sounds like your boyfriend
is trying to be considerate.
Remember how awkward
our first meeting was?
It's best for us to meet up properly
and get a fresh start!
And that's why...
Hello! I'm Shizuka's mother!
Thank you for coming today.
Not at all.
I'm sorry for barging in on you that day.
No, the fault is all mine.
Here, for you.
Manju? How lovely!
What should I even talk about?
Is this gonna be...
one of those "are you thinking
about marriage" conversations?
It's way too early for that!
Really? You do that too?
That's so impressive!
I wonder if Akira-san is thinking
about what happened before...
Yes, of course.
Maybe I'll hire you sometime!
Come by anytime!
Oh, that's wonderful!
Thank you, Tonome-san!
Thank him for what?!
What, weren't you listening?
He's giving me a 30%
"girlfriend's mother"
discount on any future investigations!
GIRLFRIEND'S MOTHER
Is that what this is about, Mom?!
And don't you encourage her, Akira-san!
My mother is very incorrigible!
You seem to be good friends.
What do you want to hire him for, anyway?
Check your father for infidelity, maybe?
Just kidding!
That's not funny in the slightest!
I'm sorry my mother is so brazen.
Not at all.
I was nervous about meeting
her for the first time,
but she really kept things flowing.
She's a good mom.
I'm glad you feel that way.
We also discussed something important.
Something important?
How is Shizuka doing at work?
Is she getting along with her coworkers?
Yes.
She's extremely capable.
We're all reliant on her,
myself included.
I see.
She's really out there in the world now.
I'm so glad.
Tonome-san. Please look
after my daughter.
Akira-san?
Ah. It's nothing.
SEASONAL ROSE GARDEN
We're here.
Where are we going today?
Let me give you a hint.
It smells like a flower...
A rose, perhaps?
That's right.
Shizuka-san, for you.
Is this...?
A present.
We're at a rose garden today.
I-I've never gotten a rose
from a man before!
It's like a romance novel!
Well, shall we?
It smells amazing!
Like being showered in rose petals!
Yes.
Shizuka-san, don't you want to
leave your flower in the car?
I-I want to keep it with me.
Am I coming off childish again?
I'm glad you seem to like it.
Oh, I know.
There's a cafe in
the rose garden, Shizuka-san.
They say they use rose
petals in all their sweets.
So many sweet smells!
At 12 o'clock, there's a scone.
At 3, there's a sandwich.
At 6, a tart.
At 9, a piece of cake.
Got it!
The sweets here are so adorable.
What does it mean
for sweets to be "adorable"?
They're small, topped
with fruit or cream...
And in a variety of colors, I suppose?
So good!
Adorable.
You've got cream on your cheek.
O-Oh, thank you.
Welcome back!
I know that voice...
Karma-san?
Shizuka-chan. Excellent right hook!
I'm sorry. You startled me.
Didn't I tell you to wait here quietly?
So, what do you want from me today?
What's with the cold shoulder, man?!
Where's Light-san?
Oh... She had other plans, apparently.
She usually tells me when she's
got plans, but this time...
Why?
I'll just be gone for a while.
So my day's pretty free,
and I came by to hang!
I brought you some tea!
Today's a work day for us, you know.
Hey, don't do me like that!
I might look like a cool loner,
but I actually need people around!
I don't see how this is my problem.
Tonome-chan, are you nice
to everyone but me?
Speak of the devil, it's my honey!
Hi! It's your sweet little dark elf bae!
But why?!
Come on, tell me!
Wait! Wait!
Karma-san?
Light... went back to her parents.
Does this mean...
DIVORCE
Divorce is looming?!
I'm sure it's not! Probably.
Don't make it sound
like it's on the table!
Why not go home and call her back?
You're just trying to get rid of me!
Screw that! I'm staying put!
What?
If I have to be alone,
I'll self-destruct from worry!
Aren't you a grown man?
Akira-san...
Can't we humor him
for just a little while?
You mean it?!
Looks like we're roomies
tonight, Tonome-chan!
Don't worry! I'll help out!
Wait. You're staying... with me?
ALARM - SNOOZE
STOP
You up?
Morning!
Would you like a meal?
Would you like a bath?
Or would you like...?
Psych!
Please leave.
There's more miso soup
where that came from!
Karma-san. Have you called Light-san yet?
Nah, still too scared to ask!
I'll just be staying a li'l while longer!
WHITE MISO
Please don't.
Mornin' all!
Good morning!
A-Akira-san? Wh-What's wrong?
You seem a bit down...
He looks the same to me.
Shizuka-san...
Don't you worry!
I attended to every single
need of my dearest Tonome-chan!
He's got energy and happiness to spare!
Please stop talking.
And stop phrasing things so suggestively.
Aw, Tonome-chan, you're no fun!
Akira-san?
It's nothing. I'm feeling
a lot better now that I'm with you.
Hey, so...
As a thanks for letting me
crash with you...
I'll help you with your
detective work today.
So he's the target?
Yes, that's right.
I'm supposed to follow him,
but if he flies, I'll probably lose him.
Sounds hopeless.
Yes.
That makes it a rather difficult job.
I don't need your h—
So you just gotta make sure
he can't fly, right?
Karma-san?
I'm going home.
What's up?
My wings feel heavy. They won't move.
Karma-san. What did you just do?
I put a curse on him.
Dark elves can use curses
to dampen the abilities of others.
But I've gotta be
in a dark headspace for it to work.
This one seemed very effective.
Well... I might get divorced, so yeah.
He's more pressed than I thought.
Karma-san. You can stay
with me again today.
For real?!
In exchange, please call your wife.
For real?
Go on.
Y'know, Tonome-chan,
I can't see your face...
But you're kind of intimidating.
Shall I dial the number for you?
No! I can do it!
I'm fine!
Then do it yourself!
They've been at this for an hour.
No! I need to get in the right headspace!
- It's best to jump in head-first!
- W-Wait!
It's like they're
good friends?
LIGHT
LIME AUDIO
Hello?
Honey!
Yeah, yeah.
I...
Yeah.
Got it. Bye.
What did she say?
Sorry, Tonome-chan!
I gotta go home!
I wonder what they talked about.
I don't know,
but I'm exhausted.
I feel like a typhoon just blew through.
Don't you like Karma-san, Akira-san?
Well... I think we're just
opposite personalities.
And it's possible...
I'm jealous of how
emotionally expressive he is.
Would you... like to be more expressive?
Well, then...
Bring it on!
Shizuka-san?
Wait, is there someone here with us?!
No, it's just the two of us.
Then get right to it!
You mean...
Head on the shoulder?
I'm not too heavy?
Um...
What are you doing?
I'm patting your head.
Invisible people don't have that custom.
You don't like it?
I'm not sure how I feel about it.
Th-That's enough.
Thank you, though.
Shizuka-san?
I thought I might touch more
of your face while I'm at it!
If you like, please.
I don't get a lot of chances
to really feel out people's faces!
What about your family?
I don't even touch my family that much!
Then...
I'm going to touch your face, too.
When I really think about it,
it's strange for skin to have colors.
Shadows, too.
And it's funny how it changes color
with your blood flow.
I won't be defeated!
Hizuha-ha. Dassh my mouf.
I'm sorry!
EPISODE 5: IT WAS MY FIRST, SO...
TO BE CONTINUED
'Sokah.